<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cyber200</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cyber200</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Security Audit Report Template</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/security-audit-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/security-audit-reports/</guid>
      <description>1. Executive Summary Objective The objective of this security audit was to evaluate the current security posture of ABC Corporation’s IT infrastructure, identify vulnerabilities, and provide actionable recommendations to enhance security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review and Audit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/review-and-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/review-and-audit/</guid>
      <description>Infrastructure and Control Audits Controls: The measures an organization takes to reduce risk.&#xA;Preventive: Security measures to stop an event from occurring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk Evaluation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/risk-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/risk-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>Tools and Techniques for Risk Evaluation Risk Matrix: A visual tool that plots risks on a grid based on their likelihood and impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defensive Techniques</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/defensive-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/defensive-techniques/</guid>
      <description>Network Security Firewalls: Firewalls act as a barrier between trusted and untrusted networks. They monitor and control incoming and outgoing network traffic based on predetermined security rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offensive Techniques</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/offensive-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/offensive-techniques/</guid>
      <description>Reconnaissance Passive Reconnaissance&#xA;Footprinting: Gathering information about the target without directly interacting with it. This includes collecting data from publicly available sources such as websites, social media, and public records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Principles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/security-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/security-principles/</guid>
      <description>CIA Triad Confidentiality: Keeping data secret or private. Integrity: Ensuring the legitimacy of data so it can be trusted. Availability: Ensuring networks, systems, and applications are up and running.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Significant Virus Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/significant-virus-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/significant-virus-events/</guid>
      <description>1971 - The Creeper Virus: created by Bob Thomas, is often considered the first computer virus. It was designed as an experimental self-replicating program that infected ARPANET systems, displaying the message &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the creeper: catch me if you can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log Management In Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/log-management-in-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/log-management-in-linux/</guid>
      <description>Managing logs on a Linux system is crucial for maintaining system health, diagnosing issues, and ensuring security. common methods and tools are:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Systemd Journal And Var-log</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/systemd-journal-and-var-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/systemd-journal-and-var-log/</guid>
      <description>Clomparison Feature /var/log systemd Journal Compatibility Good for legacy systems Better for modern, systemd-based systems Access Simple text files, easy access Requires journalctl but offers powerful features Log Management Managed by logrotate Automatic management with systemd Security Plain text, easier to tamper with More secure, tamper-resistant Filtering and Searching Basic text processing tools Advanced filtering with journalctl Centralization Logs scattered across multiple files Centralized logging Metadata Limited metadata Rich metadata Disk Usage Manual configuration and management Automatic disk usage management Persistence Requires manual setup with logrotate Configurable persistent storage Practical Recommendations Hybrid Approach: Use both /var/log and the systemd journal to take advantage of the strengths of each.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Drivers In Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/network-drivers-in-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/network-drivers-in-linux/</guid>
      <description>Overview These drivers facilitate Ethernet connectivity, managing the transmission and reception of data packets over network connections.Some commonly used network drivers in Linux operating systems, categorized by the type of Ethernet interfaces they manage:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSH master</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ssh-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ssh-master/</guid>
      <description>Overview SSH (Secure Shell) is a protocol used to securely connect to remote systems over an unsecured network, It was designed to replace earlier insecure protocols such as Telnet, rlogin, and FTP by providing a secure channel over an unsecured network by using a client-server architecture, encryption, and authentication mechanisms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Pages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/cloudflare-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/cloudflare-pages/</guid>
      <description>What is Cloudflare Pages? Cloudflare Pages is a JAMstack platform for deploying static websites. As part of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s suite of web performance and security services, Cloudflare Pages leverages the global Cloudflare network to deliver high-speed, secure, and scalable web experiences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Github Actions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/github-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/github-action/</guid>
      <description>What is GitHub Actions? GitHub Actions is a CI/CD (Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment) platform that allows developers to automate their build, test, and deployment pipelines directly from their GitHub repositories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Terminal Multiplexer: TMUX</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/tmux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/tmux/</guid>
      <description>What is tmux? tmux, short for terminal multiplexer, is a powerful command-line utility that allows users to manage multiple terminal sessions from a single window.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
